(Past Leonard:)I don't understand.
(Past Leonard:)If people don't go in there,
and you're people and....
(Past Leonard:)You are people, aren't you?
(Past Leonard:)Making a joke.
(Past Sheldon:)Do you do this often?
(Past Leonard:)On occasion.
(Past Sheldon:)Your room.
You may wanna repaint.
(Penny:)And after all that you just moved in?
I didn't just move in.
First we had to iron out a few details.
"Roommates agree
that Friday nights shall be reserved...
(Past Sheldon:)...for watching Joss Whedon's
brilliant new series, Firefly."
(Past Leonard:)Does that really need to be
in the agreement?
(Past Sheldon:)Might as well settle it now,
it's gonna be on for years.
(Past Sheldon:)Initial here.
(Past Sheldon:)All right, that's television and movies.